Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Give me your hand.
What for?
My puppy.
Hey, we ordered something delicious for you.
Aren’t you guys spoiling me too much?
We were scared out of our minds.
Thank you, guys, for worrying about me.
You’re welcome.
I’ll take P’Niran home.
We’re going the same way anyway.
I have a question.
Can we be a couple now?
Turn your face toward me.
I’m not going to answer directly.
I thought you left the lights on.
I was coming in to turn them off.
It’s past your bedtime.
Why haven’t you gone to bed?
I couldn’t sleep,
so I got up to read some more.
What’s on your mind?
Why couldn’t you sleep?
P’Cheewin.
Hmm?
How does it feel to be in love?
I like him, but I just don’t know what’s next.
Am I trying to win him over
the way people do?
Should I do anything more?
It’s so hard.
Even harder than
learning about the universe.
I’m so confused.
Every time I see him, I’m always
thinking about what we should talk about.
I keep accidentally talking about
what I’m interested in and what I know.
What has he said?
He always seems to listen
until I finish talking.
Oh, then that’s good.
How is that not good?
It’s good.
I want to keep seeing him every day.
I want to stay by his side like this forever.
Actually, it’s like—
It’s like Dad and Mom, right?
When Dad goes to work,
Mom follows to cheer him on.
They’re always together.
That’s what you mean, right?
Yes.
Well, then.
Just ask Niran to be your boyfriend.
I’ve already asked.
What?
Already?
What did he say?
Did he reject you?
He didn’t say anything.
Hmm…
Then ask again.
Ask him again when you see him.
Ask until he gives you an answer.
One more thing.
Make a bigger move.
A billion times bigger.
It’s actually a good idea to keep asking.
I’m not going to answer directly.
Love isn’t complicated.
Whatever you feel,
just follow your feelings.
I’m rooting for you, brother.
P’Niran will accept my love one day.
No matter how many
million light-years away it is,
I will get there.
Mm.
Are you sure
you don’t want to bring your crutch?
I’ll be fine.
You could’ve just waited inside your house.
I only injured one leg.
I can still walk on the other.
Hey, come on.
You’re already bothering him,
and now you’re getting on his nerves too?
Not a bother at all.
I’m free this week.
I’m dropping my brother off at school anyway.
We really are bothering you.
Are you sure
you don’t want us to help pay for gas?
It’s expensive these days.
It’s no trouble at all.
I’m very happy to help.
Besides,
Cheewa gets company on his ride to school.
Alright then.
But still,
please take this with you to eat.
Thank you.
No worries.
Cheewa.
Yes?
Say thank you to him.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
When I’m free, please let me drive Cheewa and Niran to school for a change.
Of course.
I should get going.
Okay.
Bye.
Drive safe.
I will.
Cheewa.
Here.
Why are they staring?
Why does our school
have morning assemblies?
I know, right?
Whoa.
Do you want to take some days off?
You don’t want me to graduate
at the same time as you guys?
It’s just a hurt leg.
I could still kick you right now,
Come on.
You’re so tough, huh?
Next time,
don’t push yourself too hard again. Got it?
We’re all worried about you.
But…
probably not as much as Cheewa is.
Why the hell are you shy?
You weren’t shy when you
rode on his back home the other day.
Well, my leg hurt.
And he lives near my house.
I’m shy? My ass.
Or do you want to give me a piggyback ride?
Huh?
All three of you.
There it is.
You’re shy right now.
What do you mean? I’m not shy.
You’re shy.
Admit it.
Will you guys stop teasing me already?
Yes, please stop teasing him.
Mm.
P’Niran doesn’t want you guys to know
he’s shy.
Are you on my side or theirs?
Huh? Whose side are you really on?
I could be by your side.
Yeah.
If you’re still not taken.
Guys.
Yes?
Can I date your friend now?
Huh?
I asked him, but he wouldn’t answer.
So I’m asking you guys.
You’re his best friends.
I thought you might know the answer.
I might be good at studying,
but I know nothing about this.
Seriously.
Let’s change the topic already.
If not, I’ll throw you one by one.
And we’re going to
get food from Auntie Tang’s today.
Not anywhere else.
What’s wrong with you?
It’s still early.
We haven’t even started lining up yet.
You’re getting nervous already.
Yeah.
What’s wrong?
Auntie Tang’s as always. Never changes.
Loyal to one and only.
I think Cheewa is getting down bad.
What have you done to my brother?
Yeah.
Why did you change him?
Let’s go get some dessert.
Stay here.
I’m going to buy a lollipop
to sweeten things up for you.
Okay.
Get me the same flavor.
Did you know?
I like you just the same.
Gosh.
He’s down bad.
No one has a crush on me.
I want some dessert too.
“Wait here.”
“I’m going to get you some dessert.”
By the way, Niran,
can I ask you something?
So, what’s the deal?
He’s coming on to you this hard.
Has he asked you to be his boyfriend?
When will you become a couple?
Or are you already a couple?
We’re not dating!
Sit down properly.
You guys look freaking hilarious.
My friends.
Damn it.
Well…
Yeah, you got it.
The kid seems to keep trying to win me over.
You guys know that.
I’m just going along with it.
We don’t know.
Yeah, what do you mean
by going along with it?
Do you like him hitting on you?
You guys give me such a headache,
you know?
What’s with you guys?
Whoa!
You’re pretty heavy.
Dude, go on a diet. I’m begging you.
You’re really heavy.
So damn heavy.
I can walk.
Ouch!
Sorry.
You guys are the worst.
We’ll go.
You two can help each other walk.
I don’t want to wait.
Romantic scenes are always in slow motion.
We can’t wait that long.
See you later.
You’re so extra.
It’s just lunch.
I could’ve gone with my friends.
But I want to go with you
and I have something to tell you.
P’Cheewin is picking us up
a bit late this evening.
I need to prepare for the tri-school game.
Oh, it’s coming up?
Yes, it’s next week.
That’s why the whole student council is busy.
It’s okay. Just do your work. I can wait.
Do you want to stay with me while I work?
But…
I don’t think you should.
There are so many people
on the basketball court.
You’re not feeling very well.
Just do whatever you want.
Right now, I’m hungry.
I’m starving.
Let’s go get something to eat.
You’re right.
I’m really craving food from Auntie Tang.
Let me help you walk.
Thank god you’re not carrying me
like last time.
Walk carefully.
Carry me then.
Do you have a lot of work at school?
Cheewa told me to pick you guys up late
because he needs to prepare some stuff.
Yes.
We have a school event next week.
Oh.
It’s a sports event where students from
three schools come together to compete.
Our school is the host this year.
I see.
So the student council
needs to prepare for that.
Are you competing in anything?
Oh.
Look at my leg.
I don’t think I can compete with anyone.
Oh, right.
Other people have been practicing sports.
Meanwhile,
I’ve been taking naps while waiting
for Cheewa in the student council’s room.
That’s good.
Wait until you recover
before you get back into action again.
Yeah.
By the way, Niran,
are you happy with Cheewa?
Yeah, I am.
Then I’ll be picking you up
and dropping you off at school
until your leg has healed.
Oh, you really don’t have to.
I don’t want to bother you.
I can ask my dad to pick me up.
Hey.
It’s okay.
I can drop you off.
I have to drop Cheewa off anyway
Besides,
I get food from your dad
every morning.
That’s amazing.
Alright, whatever’s convenient for you.
I’m okay with anything.
Thank you, big bro.
Of course, little bro.
(Hi, P’Niran.)
Oh.
- Were you asleep?
- (What’s up?)
Sorry.
I can talk.
Is everything alright?
Oh, I just wanted to ask if we’re meeting
at the same time tomorrow morning.
(Same time.)
Or do you want to leave earlier or later?
No, I’m just asking.
Okay.
Then let’s meet at the same time.
(Were you exhausted today?)
You fell asleep in the car too.
(I’m so exhausted.)
I want to keep talking to you,
but it feels like I’m about to pass out, P’Niran.
You can go back to sleep.
We can talk tomorrow.
(P’Niran.)
Yes?
I might’ve been pretty busy
with the school event lately,
(and I might not have time
to tell you this often,)
(but I’m still the same in every way.)
I miss you every day.
(I still like you the same.)
Mm.
Go to sleep.
Okay.
Good night.
Mm. Good night.
(Got it.)
You can pick me up later tomorrow
so you can have more time to sleep.
Cheewa.
Are you asleep?
(Okay. I’ll hang up.)
Tomorrow,
I’ll be waiting to see you.
The game starts at 1.
Wanna go watch?
You mean basketball?
Yes, come watch me compete.
Hello.
Hey, guys.
I saw Jace,
the guy Niran always talked about
when he was trying out for the national team.
Huh? Where did you see him?
Here?
Yeah.
I saw him walking with Coach Ong.
The student council was there too.
I guess they were filming
promotional content for the tri-school game.
It’s today.
The basketball game looks so good.
The top contenders from the other schools
are fire.
Who do we even have left from our school?
Not many seniors are competing.
Why don’t you ask Cheewa?
He’s preparing for the event.
He should know.
By the way, he’s been so busy
he hasn’t eaten with us for several days now.
Have you talked to him at all?
Not really.
We’ve only seen each other in the car.
He seems tired.
He sleeps the whole way.
When I saw Jomyut and Newton, they were
complaining that they were tired too.
They have no time
to get on our nerves like before.
I miss them.
Those three with glasses.
Glasses is here.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Don’t you have to work?
I’m done with my work.
The game starts at 1.
Wanna go watch?
You mean basketball?
Yes, come watch me compete.
Huh?
You’re competing in basketball?
Yes, they were short on players,
so they asked me to fill in.
Okay. Sure.
We’ll go watch you.
We’re free this afternoon.
See you later.
Someone this timid
is competing in basketball?
Does he even know how to play?
Maybe he’s a substitute.
He said they were short on players.
But even though he’s a sub,
we need to go cheer him on.
Yeah, I know.
So?
Do we want to go wait at the court now?
You’re so impatient.
I don’t have anything else to do.
Oh, I have class, but I’m not studying.
Ugh.
You’ll fall asleep.
You should study for a change.
There they are.
You guys are late.
They’re about to start.
Well,
we were waiting for Hem
to get his meatballs.
Where’s Cheewa?
Has he gotten ready?
Gotten ready? He’s already on the court.
Damn.
Niran, he’s a starter?
So cool.
Without his glasses too.
Of course, Cheewa’s a starter.
He’s been practicing for a week.
Oh.
He said he was preparing for the event.
I thought he was organizing it.
He was organizing the event
and practicing basketball.
That’s why he’s super exhausted.
At first, we asked him
why he had to play basketball.
Did you know what his answer was?
He said he wanted to look cool
in front of the person he likes.
Bravo!
Are you waiting to talk to him?
The judo match is about to start.
Wanna watch it?
You guys go ahead.
I’ll catch up with you soon.
- Alright.
- Okay.
See you later.
P’Cheewa, you’re so handsome.
I’m your fan, P’Cheewa.
We’re your biggest fans.
You’re amazing.
Thank you.
Meow kiss, please.
This camera too, please.
You’re getting way too cool.
Damn, Jace beat our school again.
What’s wrong?
Niran!
I’m going to the Music Club with these two.
Is something going on?
I just wanted to ask about our last match,
when you lost to me.
You weren’t giving it your all, were you?
You don’t usually slip up that easily.
If you lost on purpose,
just tell me honestly.
I don’t want to win that way.
You…
I’m what?
Are you crazy?
Huh?
What kind of person do you think I am?
Do you really think I’d want to lose to you?
After that match, I was down for like a month.
Why would I lose on purpose?
What are you even thinking?
Well, you’re usually better than me.
Hey, rankings go up and down.
No one stays at the top forever.
I always give it my all.
I never go easy on my opponents.
I really lost. I admit it.
And you…
You won, so be proud of yourself.
Give yourself some credit.
Don’t think you won
because I went easy on you.
I like someone cool like you.
Of course. I’m Niran.
Win or lose, I’m still cool.
Can I get your number, cool guy?
What for?
Why are you staring?
What’s wrong, Cheewa?
Nothing.
That’s a lie.
Yes.
Is Jace hitting on you?
Huh?
He asked for your number.
Did you give it to him?
What did you talk to him about?
Did you two hit it off?
Why? Are you jealous, kid?
Am I allowed to be jealous?
If so, I’m very jealous.
Jace asked for my number.
He said he wanted to get to know me better.
But I didn’t give it to him.
I said
we’re better off as rivals
and that he shouldn’t
want to be something else.
Whoa, that’s so harsh.
I really believe that,
so I rejected him directly.
So the fact that you didn’t reject me directly
means…
I have a chance to be something else?
What about you, Cheewa?
Don’t you have so many admirers yourself?
You just took off your glasses
and played basketball.
What’s with all that?
They asked for photos with me.
They just said I’m good at basketball.
I didn’t know
you were that good at basketball.
I beat you before, P’Niran.
Am I cool?
But now you’re cool
in other people’s eyes too.
Let’s not talk about other people.
In your eyes, am I any cool at all?
Well…
You’re pretty cool.
Kinda cool.
That’s enough.
I told other people
I’m already seeing someone.
Since when
have you been seeing someone?
Will you?
Huh?
Will P’Niran be Cheewa’s boyfriend?
By the way, you said
you wanted to come over
and listen to the music my dad plays.
But…
you want me to listen to music at your house
as what, exactly?
Hello.
Come over as often as you like.
Will your dad really be okay with this?
Of course.
I just don’t really invite anyone over.
Thara was here once.
He was hanging out for just a little while
before I kicked him out.
Look at you, all stressed and down.
Don’t be so down.
You have me. I’ve got you.
It’s my house.
Okay?
Okay.
Come on.
P’Niran, you’re talented just like your dad.
Oh, my dad.
If he hadn’t gotten so badly injured
that he couldn’t do judo anymore,
he’d be so damn intense.
Bam! Bam! Bam!
What are you teasing me about?
Hello.
Do you play any sports, Cheewa?
I play some,
but I’m not very serious about it.
He says he’s not very serious,
but he won a basketball game today.
Wow.
Amazing.
Hey.
Don’t you want to be a professional athlete?
Hmm…
Yeah, but it’s more like a hobby for me.
Cheewa is good at everything.
He can play guitar.
He’s good at school.
He’s good at everything he does.
Niran, take it down a notch.
I’m asking Cheewa,
but you answer for him.
You know everything about him, huh?
What’s with you?
Is P’Niran always this talkative?
Oh, he was so chatty as a kid.
He’d talk non-stop.
Yeah.
But now that he’s grown up,
he won’t talk to me.
He acts all cool.
I talk to you.
You’re the only one acting all cool.
Hey.
“Wanna eat?”
“Do you want dinner?”
Like this.
Are you making fun of me?
Don’t make me tell your stories.
One day, he came home.
I don’t know what had gotten into him.
He went into the bathroom,
turned on the shower, and cried under it.
He was fully clothed, mind you.
Whoa.
When was that?
Good thing he wasn’t singing too.
Otherwise, it’d be too much.
But P’Niran is a really good singer.
Oh, you’re the best.
Really?
No need to get into this one.
There are so many stories, especially
from when he went to competitions.
That’s enough, Dad.
He didn’t want to go.
Are you sure
you don’t want to stay for dinner?
I won’t take long to cook.
My friends are coming over
to celebrate at my house.
Next time, I’ll take you up on that.
Okay.
No problem.
Come over as often as you like.
Make yourself at home here.
I’m going to go prepare dinner.
Okay. Bye.
Let’s go.
My dad seems to like you.
He doesn’t usually invite anyone
to stay for a meal.
It was fun talking to him.
I thought he’d be scary.
Oh, no. He just acts scary,
but he’s nothing like that.
He acts all cool just like you do.
Huh?
Can I really come to your house often?
Of course.
My dad already invited you.
Do you want me to come?
Well, yes.
You can come.
By the way, you said
you wanted to come over
and listen to the music my dad plays.
Remember that?
I do.
I said that while we were on the bus
to the science exhibition, but…
you want me to listen to music at your house
as what, exactly?
Huh?
You haven’t given me an answer.
What answer?
I asked you to be my boyfriend.
Well…
Here we come, Mr. Parncheewa.
Jomyut said
you’re going to order pizza, Cheewa.
Let’s go.
Where’s Newton?
He’s running an errand with his family.
Whoa.
Who is more important, his family or us?
Congrats, bro,
on winning the basketball game.
Hey.
I thought you were going to lose.
The other team was so good.
Cheewa might not look it,
but he’s actually good at so many things.
He’s done everything in the universe.
Cheewa, how many hours
do you have in a day?
My parents always encourage me
to try different things.
I can always figure out if I like them later.
Have you tried judo?
I took lessons for a little while
when I was a kid.
I only got the basics.
Where did you take your lessons?
This is Parncheewa, everyone.
He’s new. He’ll be practicing with us today.
Why?
Are you worried he’s better than you?
Come on.
You’re already good, man.
Thank you.
You’re the best in my heart.
Thara, can you pass me that?
No, the other one.
So you really took judo lessons?
Yes, I did.
Why?
Did you think I lied?
No.
It was just unexpected.
Cheewa.
Yes?
Have we met before?
I don’t know how you feel about me,
but I really admire you.
I’m impressed by everything you do.
We’ve met before, haven’t we?
My name’s Niran. I’m 8 years old.
My name’s Cheewa. I’m 7 years old.
Then P’Niran is older.
Yes, P’Niran.
From now on,
P’Niran will take care of you, Cheewa.
Okay.
Glasses, come here.
Count one, two, three.
P’Niran, you’re so good.
You’re so small. How are you so good?
It doesn’t matter if you’re big or small.
It’s all about this.
Your ribs?
Ugh.
Or…
is it about
your insides?
It’s all about your heart.
If you have the heart to fight,
you can do anything.
Come on, let’s try again.
Really focus on P’Niran’s feet.
Do you want me to focus on your feet
or your heart?
Ugh!
Cheewa!
If you want snacks,
come hide here and eat them.
If Coach sees you sneaking in snacks,
you’ll have to mop the floor.
You love snacking, P’Niran?
Mm.
You’re actually pretty heavy, Nong Cheewa.
You can let me get down, P’Niran.
I’ll be fine.
Your legs still hurt.
P’Niran can do this.
You’re so amazing, P’Niran.
One day, I’ll let you ride on my back too.
I’ll be waiting.
P’Niran, did you know
Cheewa is a human
who’s good at keeping promises?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dad, hurry!
P’Niran is going to teach me
some new moves today.
Parncheewa, today is your last judo lesson.
We’re moving tomorrow.
It’s okay.
If you like taking judo lessons,
I’ll find a new place for you.
You’ll get to meet new friends too.
But I don’t want to meet new friends.
Let’s hurry.
I don’t want to keep P’Niran waiting.
Slow down.
You don’t want to fall down the stairs.
Parncheewa,
are you waiting for Niran?
His dad called this morning to say that
Niran wasn’t coming to practice today.
Please practice with the others instead.
That day,
I felt like
I was being thrown to the floor
because I knew
it was the last day I’d get to see you.
But I didn’t get to see you,
or even get to say goodbye.
JUDO COMPETITION
Then one day, I saw you again
when you won a judo competition.
PIANGNIRAN KITTIMETEE
MEKHINWIBOON SCHOOL (M.W.B.)
I was so happy.
I was so happy I didn’t know what to do.
So I asked Dad to let me take the entrance
exam for your high school right away.
But later, I didn’t know how to act,
so I pretended not to know you.
Getting to know you again this time
makes me really happy.
Whether you remember me or not,
I’ve always remembered you.
I don’t know how you feel about me,
but I really admire you.
I’ve liked you since back then.
I’m impressed by everything you do.
No matter how you end up feeling about me,
I’ll still like you anyway.
No matter then or now.
Thank you.
Just having you in front of me right now
already makes me the happiest.
Mm.
Cheewa.
What if I asked you back?
Will you be my boyfriend?
♪ Is this love I feel, am I calling it right? ♪
♪ Is it why my heart beats faster tonight? ♪
Will you?
Will P’Niran be Cheewa’s boyfriend?
♪ I see you every day ♪
♪ Yet I miss you again ♪
♪ Is this love I feel, can you lend me a hand? ♪
♪ Come and help this heart understand ♪
- Yes!
♪ This feeling that I have ♪
♪ Oh tell me, is this love? ♪
This is how a love nerd is.
I’m only like this with you, P’Niran.
Hey, guys.
This is Nong Cheewa.
I asked him to play the drums.
You want Cheewa to play the drums?
Does he know how to play?
Is there anything you can’t do?
It seems like you can do everything.
I want you to be happy, P’Niran.
You’re spoiling me rotten, you know?
But aren’t you happy?
If you are, then let yourself be spoiled rotten.
I like every version of you.